cfapromo.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy – CFA Promo

### **Cohen-Friedberg Associates, LLC**  
**Website Privacy Policy – YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS**

This Privacy Policy applies to the sites where it appears.

This Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where it is located. By interacting with us, you consent to these practices.

We collect information from and about you.

We collect contact information. We might collect your name and street address. We might also collect your phone number or email address.

We collect information you submit or post. If you submit a question or comment or apply for a job, we will collect the information you provide to us.

We collect demographic information. We may collect information like your gender and age. We may also collect your zip code.

We collect other information. If you use our website, we may collect information about the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us.

We collect information in different ways.

We collect information directly from you. For example, if you fill out a sweepstakes or contest entry form or sign up for updates.

We collect information from you passively. We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. We collect information about users over time when you use this website. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. Learn more about these tools and how you can control them, read the “choices” section below.

We get information about you from third parties. Our business partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you.

We use information as disclosed and described here.

We use information to respond to your requests or questions. For example, we might use your information to respond to requests regarding promotions we are administering.

We use information to improve services. We may use your information to make our website better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us.

We combine information. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our clients, and our websites.

We use information to communicate with you about our relationship. We may contact you about your feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

We use information as otherwise permitted by law or as we may notify you.

We may share information with third parties.

We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us.

We will share information with our clients. Information we share with these clients is subject to their privacy policies.

We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business. For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.

You have certain choices about how we use your information.

You can control cookies and tracking tools. Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies or other tracking tools. How you do so depends on the type of tool. Certain browsers can be set to reject browser cookies.

Our Do Not Track Policy: Some websites have “do not track” features that allow you to tell a website not to track you. These features are not all uniform. We do not currently respond to those signals. If you block cookies, certain features on our websites may not work. If you block or reject cookies, not all of the tracking described here will stop.

Options you select are browser and device specific.

Your California privacy rights.

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an email, or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a “Shine the Light” inquiry.

These sites and apps are not intended for children.

Our websites are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children’s privacy on-line here.

We use standard security measures.

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet.

We store information in the United States.

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States.

This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for our business. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

We may link to other sites or apps or have third party services on our platforms we don’t control.

If you click on a third party link, you will be taken to platforms we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Read other companies’ privacy policies carefully. We are not responsible for these third parties.

Feel free to contact us if you have more questions

If you have any questions about this Policy or want to correct or update your information, please email us at eric@cfapromo.com. You can also write to us or call at (888) 371 3742

We may update this Policy.

From time to time we may change this Policy.

We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.

© 2016 Cohen-Freidberg Associates, LLC. All rights reserved.
